&gt;&gt; In 2014, Google published its own network in
&gt;&gt; 2014年 Googleは独自のネットワークを
the ImageNet competition and in homage to Yann LeCun and LeNet,
ImageNetコンペティションとホームページでYann LecunおよびLeNetに公表し
Google named their network,
Googleはそのネットワークを
wait for it, GoogLeNet.
GoogLeNetと名付けました
It's spelled like GoogleNet but it's pronounced GoogLeNet.
GoogleNetと似たスペルですが グーグラネットと発音します
Go figure.
図を見てください
In the ImageNet competition,
ImageNetコンペティションにおいて
GoogLeNet performed even a little better than VGG:
GoogLeNetはVGGより少しだけ良い成績でした
6.7% compared to 7.3% percent,
6.7％対7.3％でした
although at that level,
しかし このレベルでは
it kind of feels like we're splitting hairs.
些細な差に感じます
&gt;&gt; GoogLeNet's great advantage is that it runs really fast.
&gt;&gt; GoogLeNetの大きな利点は実行が速いことです
The team that developed GoogLeNet developed a clever concept
GoogLeNetを開発したチームは
called an Inception module, which trains really well and is efficiently deployable.
インセプションモジュールという賢い概念を開発し 実によくトレーニングされ 効率的に展開可能です
&gt;&gt; Do you remember inception?
&gt;&gt; インセプションを覚えていますか
Vincent explained the concept earlier.
ビンセントが以前にこの概念を説明しました
We're going to show it again here, in case you forgot.
念のため ここでもう一度示しておきます
&gt;&gt; It's called an inception module.
&gt;&gt; これはインセプションモジュールと呼ばれます
It's going to look a little more complicated.
もう少し複雑に見えます
The idea is that at each layer of your ConvNet,
考え方としてはConvNetの各層で
you can make a choice,
選択を行うことができ
have a pooling operation,
プーリング操作を持ち
have a convolution and then you need to decide,
畳み込みを持つことができます 決定する必要があるのは
is it the one by one convolution or a three by three or five by five.
1x1の畳み込みか 3x3か 5x5かということです
All of these are actually beneficial to the modeling power of your network.
これらはすべて ネットワークのモデリング能力にとって実際に有益です
So why choose? Let's use them all.
それでは なぜ選択するのでしょうか  すべてを使用しましょう
Here's what an inception module looks like.
これはインセプションモジュールがどのようなものかを示しています
Instead of having a single convolution,
1つの畳み込みを使用する代わりに
you have a composition of average pooling followed by one by one,
平均プーリングとその後の1x1を組み合わせることができ
then a one by one convolution,
1x1の畳み込み
then a one by one followed by a three by three,
1x1の後に3x3
then a one by one followed by a five by five and
1x1の後に5x5を使用し
at the top you simply concatenate the output of each of them.
最後にそれぞれの出力を連結できます
It looks complicated but what's interesting is that you can choose these parameters
複雑に見えますが 面白いのは これらのパラメーターを
in such a way that the total number of parameters in your model is very small,
モデル内のパラメーターの合計数が非常に少なくなるように
yet the model performs better than if you had a simple convolution.
しかも モデルが単一の畳み込みを使用した場合より改善されるように選択できることです
&gt;&gt; As Vincent says, the inception modules create
&gt;&gt; ビンセントが言うように インセプションモジュールは
a situation in which the total number of parameters is very small.
パラメーターの合計数が非常に少ない状況を作り出します
This is why GoogLeNet runs almost as fast as AlexNet.
このため GoogLeNetはAlexNetと同じくらい高速に実行します
&gt;&gt; And of course GoogLeNet has great accuracy.
&gt;&gt; そして もちろん GoogLeNetは非常に正確です
Like we mentioned earlier,
すでに述べたように
it's ImageNet error was only 7%.
ImageNetのエラーはわずか7％でした
GoogLeNet is a great choice to investigate if you need to run your network in real time,
GoogLeNetは自動運転車のようにリアルタイムでネットワークを実行する必要がある場合には
like maybe in a self-driving car.
調査すべき有力候補です